[1,0,0,[["cc.JsonAsset",["_name","json"],1]],[[0,0,1,3]],[[0,"mst_help",{"1":{"question":"Welcome to Hippo Supermarket","answer":"Dear manager, welcome to \"Hippo Supermarket\", please consult the game help if you have any difficulties in the game"},"2":{"question":"How to play?","answer":"Hippo Supermarket is a casual game with supermarket theme. Earn coin by completing orders, and use coin to unlock the buildings in the supermarket."},"3":{"question":"How to merge the items of order?","answer":"Clicking on an item in the order will pop up merge chain. An item that is not shown in the chain means that the item has not yet been merged."},"4":{"question":"What if the positions on the board are full?","answer":"You can store the items in the backpack first. If there is not enough space, please sell some items temporarily to ensure the smooth flow of the chessboard."},"5":{"question":"What to do if insufficient Energy?","answer":"Recovers Energy every 2m, and Energy can be obtained by free benefits, various gift packages and other resources."},"6":{"question":"What are coin used for?","answer":"coin are used to build supermarkets, experience can be gained from building supermarkets and used to upgrade the supermarket level."},"7":{"question":"What are diamonds used for?","answer":"Diamonds can be used to buy resources such as items, props, and rare treasure chests. They can also be used to immediately unlock cooling items and bubble items. In addition, they can also be used to purchase rare building decorations in the supermarket."},"8":{"question":"What does it mean green tick, medal, and crown on items?","answer":"A green tick means the item is required for the order; a medal means the item is needed for the VIP card daily task; a crown means the highest level item in the synthesis chain."},"9":{"question":"How to get building cosmetics?","answer":"Find the dressable building in the lobby - collection - building, click on the building decoration to get it."},"10":{"question":"How to use the costume coupon?","answer":"Find the buildings that can be decorated in the lobby - collection - buildings. Some building decorations can only be exchanged by decoration coupons."},"11":{"question":"How to get trade order rewards?","answer":"Submitting trade orders will be immediately rewarded with coin, and additional items and treasure box will be rewarded when the trade vehicle returns."},"12":{"question":"How to get hive?","answer":"Caterpillars are produced from flowers, and the highest level of the caterpillar merge chain is a beehive."},"13":{"question":"How to get candy?","answer":"Honey is produced through the hive, and the highest level of the honey merge chain is a jar of candy."},"14":{"question":"How to get the Lottery?","answer":"Combine two first-level lucky treasure box into a second-level lucky treasure box, and the second-level lucky treasure chest has a chance to produce a lottery."},"15":{"question":"How to get the fish tank?","answer":"Through the ice cubes produced by the refrigerator, the ice cubes will melt into water after a period of time, hydrated into the highest-grade water cups, and the water cups into fish tanks."},"16":{"question":"How to get pearl mussels?","answer":"The sixtieth armor is produced through the fish tank, and the highest level of the sixtieth merge chain is the pearl oyster."},"17":{"question":"How to get redemption code?","answer":"Join the game official communication group to get redemption code rewards."}}]],0,0,[],[],[]]